It's all about the music.
Camp Rock 2: The Final Jam is a comedy, music, tv
movie film directed by Paul Hoen.
Mitchie can't wait to go back to Camp Rock and spend the summer making
new music with her friends and superstar Shane Gray.
But the slick new camp across the lake, Camp Star, has drummed up some
serious competition – featuring newcomers Luke and Dana.
In a sensational battle of the bands, with Camp Rock's future at stake, will Camp Star's flashy production and
over-the-top antics win out, or will Camp Rockers prove that music, teamwork, and spirit are what truly matter?
Mitchie Torres, played by Demi Lovato.
Shane Gray, played by Joe Jonas.
Nate Gray, played by Nick Jonas.
Jason Gray, played by Kevin Jonas.
Brown Cesario, played by Daniel Fathers.
Axel Turner, played by Daniel Kash.
Camp Rock 2: The Final Jam is a 2010 musical television film directed by Paul Hoen
from a screenplay by Regina Hicks, Karin Gist, and Dan Berendsen.
The 80th Disney Channel Original Movie, the film is the sequel to Camp Rock (2008) and stars Demi
Lovato, the Jonas Brothers, Maria Canals-Barrera, Meaghan Jette Martin, and Alyson Stoner.
The film premiered on Disney Channel on September 3, 2010 (2010-09-03).
A sequel, Camp Rock 3, is in development.
The film explores themes of summer camp, battle of the
bands, camp, singing, singing competition.
The tone is lighthearted.